

# EMILIE TØNNESSEN FRONTEND DEVELOPER

# **CONTACT**



Emilie Henriette Kathenes Tønnessen



12th of January 1996



+47 99168210



emilie@tonnessen.com



www.tonnessen.com



www.github.com/emilie tonnessen

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a 26-year-old frontend developer with a lot of customer experience. I am a conscientious and responsible person with a positive attitude. I have a driving force where I constantly work to improve myself as a person and in my line of work. I have a good eye for details and see what needs to be done.

I am humble and have no problem acknowledging mistakes or potential for improvement, and constructive criticism is well received. I am a team player and enjoy working with others, but also very independent and structured to work well by myself.

#### HTML

#### CSS

- Sass
- Material UI
- JSS
- Bootstrap

#### JavaScript

- React JS
- Next JS
- TypeScript
- Redux

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

As a Frontend Developer I am well known with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. When writing JavaScript, I prefer writing it in TypeScript.

Out of all the frameworks for JavaScript I am most experienced in React + TypeScript. I also have experience with Next.js as I wrote my final exam with that framework.

For styling I have the most experience with Sass and Material UI, but I also have experience using JSS and Bootstrap.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Apr. 2022 - present Berg-Hansen Reisebureau AS Oslo

Working as a Frontend Developer to create a new booking solution for Berg-Hansen's self-service website. We use technology such as React combined with

TypeScript, Material UI and Redux.

Jun. 2021 – Mar. 2022 Hurtigruten Group AS Oslo

Worked as a Frontend Developer at Hurtigruten Group for their B2B team. We used React with TypeScript and libraries like Redux. For styling we used MaterialUI and

JSS.

2017 – 2018 Adecco Asker and Bærum

Kindergarten Substitute

2016 – 2017 **Maxbo** Vækerø

Extra help on lumber dept.

2016 Maxbo Vækerø

Timber Seller, 100%

2014 - 2015 **Monter** Risør

Extra help and seasonal staff on lumber dept.

2013 – 2014 Risør Steinsenter Risør

Seasonal staff

## **EDUCATION**

#### 2019 - 2021 Frontend Development

Noroff - School of Technology and Digital Media, Online

## 2016 - 2019 Privatist

Sonans Oslo

## 2012 - 2014 VGS ST Toppidrett Hest

Melsom VGS

#### 2002 - 2012 Grunnskole

Risør barne- og ungdomsskole

## **COURSES**

#### Advanced CSS and Sass (Udemy)

"The most advanced and modern CSS course on the internet: master flexbox, CSS Grid, responsive design, and so much more."

## **Unit Testing Jest (Udemy)**

"Master unit testing with NodeJs, Typescript, Jest and React. Write top quality Typescript and NodeJs software with Jest"